awesomeweb.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy · AwesomeWeb

As used in this Privacy Policy, “AwesomeWeb” refers to all websites, properties, and services owned or operated by AwesomeWeb Ltd.

This Privacy Policy is part of AwesomeWeb’s Terms of Use and describes the privacy practices of AwesomeWeb. It explains when and how AwesomeWeb collects end user and client information, including Personally Identifiable Information (defined below), how we use such information, and the circumstances under which we may disclose such information to others.

By visiting the AwesomeWeb website or registering for our service, you acknowledge that you accept and consent to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies other than AwesomeWeb, or to individuals whom AwesomeWeb does not employ or manage, including any of the third parties to which AwesomeWeb may disclose information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Please refer to the privacy policies of these third parties for information concerning their privacy practices. 

## What Information Does AwesomeWeb Collect?

### Visitors to the AwesomeWeb Website

If you are a visitor to the AwesomeWeb website or an AwesomeWeb user (“User”) who registers or signs into the AwesomeWeb website, we may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device, which may include information that can itself be used to identify and/or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”):

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Phone Number
  * Website Name and URL
  * Profile Photo
  * Portfolio Information
  * Client Endorsement Information
  * Client Message Information
  * Credit Card Number
  * Billing Address
  * Visitor Site Preferences

AwesomeWeb may also receive certain information that may be provided by your browser or mobile device, including:

  * Browser Information
  * Operating System Information
  * Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)
  * IP Address
  * Pages Accessed
  * Time of Visit
  * Time of Last Visit
  * Referring Site, Application, or Service, including the relevant Search Queries that led you to AwesomeWeb’s Website

### Visitors to the AwesomeBlog

If you wish to access certain functions within the AwesomeBlog, such as posting comments, subscribing to AwesomeBlog, or registering for webinars, we may ask you to provide information, including:

  * Name
  * Email Address
  * Website Name and URL

## How Do We Use This Information?

### Visitors to the AwesomeWeb Website

We use the AwesomeWeb User Information, including Personally Identifiable Information, to register your account, fulfill your requests, understand how you are engaging with AwesomeWeb, communicate with you, determine if you are satisfied with the Service, process billing for AwesomeWeb Services, and personalize your experience on the AwesomeWeb website and with the AwesomeWeb Service.

We may also use AwesomeWeb User Information to facilitate the delivery of content or advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you about new or existing products and services or special offers. For more informationion opting out of these communications, please see the section on “User Privacy Controls” below.

### Visitors to the AwesomeBlog

We may use information you voluntarily provide when visiting the AwesomeBlog to send you e-mail communications, such as information on upcoming events, and to understand how you are engaging with and perceive AwesomeWeb Services.

## Our Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties

### Service Providers

Information, including AwesomeWeb’s User Data and any Personally Identifiable Information contained therein, may be shared with certain third-party companies and individuals that help facilitate technical and administrative aspects of the AwesomeWeb Service (e.g. credit card processing and escrow banking service), or perform functions related to the administration of AwesomeWeb (e.g. hosting services). These third parties perform tasks on our behalf and are contractually obligated not to disclose or use AwesomeWeb’s User Data for any other purpose, and to employ adequate security measures to prevent unauthorized access to such data. However, AwesomeWeb is not responsible in the event that Personally Identifiable Information is disclosed as a result of a breach or security lapse by any such third party.

### Law Enforcement and Legal Process

AwesomeWeb also reserves the right to disclose any AwesomeWeb User Data (including Personally Identifiable Information) to: (i) comply with any law, regulation, or legal request; (ii) enforce, apply, or investigate breaches of the Terms of Use or other agreements; (iii) respond to client requests; or (iv) protect the rights, property, user experience, or safety of AwesomeWeb, our employees, our users, or others.

### Change of Control

If AwesomeWeb, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by another company or successor entity, AwesomeWeb’s User Data will be one of the assets transferred or acquired by the purchaser or successor. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any purchaser of or successor to AwesomeWeb or its assets may continue to collect, use and disclose your information acquired prior to such transfer or acquisition as set forth in this policy.

## How We Protect Your Personal Information

AwesomeWeb has implemented reasonable security mechanisms to protect AwesomeWeb User Data that is maintained on AwesomeWeb’s servers from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

However, please keep in mind that no security system is impenetrable. It may be possible for third parties to intercept or access AwesomeWeb’s User Data in spite of these measures. AwesomeWeb cannot guarantee the security of your information and cannot be held responsible for unauthorized access to AwesomeWeb client accounts.

## User Privacy Controls

If you have an online account with AwesomeWeb, you can log in, update your account information, and request to deactivate your account from the Settings page. You may also unsubscribe from any of our email or direct message communications regarding updates or products by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any message or from your Email Settings area.

## AwesomeWeb’s Use of Cookies

“Cookies” are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services. We use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session, and we use data collection devices (such as Google Analytics), including cookies, on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety, to offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie and to allow us to provide information that is targeted to your interests. We link the information we store in our cookies to personally identifiable information you submit when you create an AwesomeWeb account. We may use third-party service provides to assist us in monitoring your use of the Site. Information collected by these cookies is also governed by this privacy policy.

## Email Communications

We may contact you by email or other equivalent electronic communications if you access AwesomeWeb Services. By registering or using AwesomeWeb, you specifically consent to the receipt of these e-mail or text message communications. If you do not want to receive emails or other communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions in the body of such communications or update your account settings.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued access to or use of AwesomeWeb following constructive notice of material changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute consent to any amendments and/or modifications.

## Questions & Comments

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact AwesomeWeb at support@awesomeweb.com.

**Last updated: September 17, 2014**
